(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)Hi, how was the screening?
(Leonard:)Oh, Sheldon invoked Rosa Parks
(Leonard:)to make somebody who
cut the line feel bad,
(Leonard:)but only the
white people felt bad.
(Penny:)Ugh, I should've never bought
him that coloring book
(Penny:)that explains
Black History Month.
(Leonard:)How'd it go with my mother?
(Penny:)Uh, you know,
it started a little rocky,
(Penny:)but I think we got
to a good place.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Leonard:)Well done.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Yeah, and when I dropped her off
at the hotel,
(Penny:)she even gave me a hug.
(Leonard:)Did she think
you were choking or...
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, that's great.
(Leonard:)Thank you for
spending time with her.
(Penny:)No problem.
(Penny:)Um, so listen,
(Penny:)I don't know if you have
any plans next weekend,
(Penny:)but I kind of promised your mom
(Penny:)we'd have another
wedding ceremony
(Penny:)so she could attend this time.
(Leonard:)Wait, we're gonna
get married again?
(Penny:)Yeah, kind of, but now we can
invite our friends and family.
(Leonard:)Seems like a lot
of trouble for a hug.
(Penny:)Come on, it'll be fun,
(Penny:)and, you know, your mom
was genuinely hurt
(Penny:)we didn't invite her
to the first one.
Look, in our defense,